INFO

Residence

Morocco, Berrechid

Nationality

Morocco

Birthdate

1998/10/14

Gender

Male

Phone

+212680096104

Email

abdo.zad.raja2@gmail.com

SKILLS

BACKEND

LARAVEL
PHP
REST API
SQL
GRAPH QL
JAVA

FRONTEND

VUEJS
ANGULAR JS
REACT NATIVE
HTML
CSS
JS
BOOTSTRAP

DATABASE

JQUERY

VUFX

MYSQL
SQL SERVER
ORACLE DB
SQL LITE
FIREBASE

MODELING

UML •••••
MERISE ••••

DISKTOP

C#
.NET
JAVA

ZADELKHAIR ABDELKODDOUS

Full stack web developer

PROFILE

My name is ABDELKODDOUS ZADELKHAIR I'm 23 years old, full stack web developer (LARAVEL & VUEJS) with a vast array of knowledge in many different front end and back end languages, responsive frameworks, databases, desktop and mobile applications (C# and JAVA). and best coding practices.

EDUCATION

2020 - 2021 **Bachlor Of Computer Science** University Ibn Zohr. Taroudant i got my bachelor of computer science with honor degree (16/20). 2018 - 2020 **Skilled Technician in Software Development Diploma** ISTICG OFPPT, Berrechid I got this diploma in software development with honor degree (17/20). 2016 - 2017 **Height School Diploma** Ouled Hriz. Berrechid high school diploma scientific Ouled Hriz Berrechid.

EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present stock management system

direction des impôts, Marrakech

Stock management application for the human resources department of the tax administration in Marrakech

2021 - Present elwadifa.info

freelance job announcement website.

2021 - 3 traineeship at AGRI4.0

months

Agri 4.0, AGADIR
3-month internship at the agri 4.0 company, I developed during this internship a mobile application that manages a nursery with reactnative laravel technology.

2020 - 5 Frontend developer at ZadTech

months

ZadTech, Elmohammadia

Frontend developer (vuejs and angular) at zadtech company.

